http://www.jtbworld.com/privacy-policy

HomeSoftwareCADBlogAboutContact
Privacy Policy
JTB World
JTB World recognizes that respecting user privacy over the Internet is of utmost importance. This privacy statement is designed to provide information about the privacy and data collection practices for the site: jtbworld.com. The Site is operated by JTB World.
If you have questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy statement, you should contact us at info@jtbworld.com.
Identifying Information.
In general, you can visit the Site without telling us who you are or providing any information about yourself. In some areas of the Site, we ask you to provide information that will enable us to process an order, offer services that require registration, assist you with technical support issues or to follow up with you. Generally, JTB World requests identifying information when you:
Contact us by e-mail, phone or other means.
Place an order.
Provide feedback to an online survey or tell us about an idea or suggestion.
Participate in a rebate program, contest, or other promotional offer.
Request information or files from technical support or customer service.
In these instances, JTB World may ask for Personal Data like your name, address, e-mail address, phone number and other appropriate information needed to provide you with these services.
We may use your Personal Data to contact you with newsletters, marketing or promotional materials and other information that may be of interest to you.
In all instances, if you receive a newsletter or other mailing from us, you will always be able to "unsubscribe" to these mailings at any time.
What JTB World Will Do With Your Information.
If you choose to give us personal information for any of the purposes above, this information is retained by JTB World and will only be used by
JTB World to support your customer relationship with us. We will only contact you if further information is required from you to complete a service or to inform you about relevant news, something you always can opt out from receiving. If your company does not want to be listed publicly as a customer or reference contact us to be removed.
What Others May Do With Your Information.
JTB World does not share, rent, or sell any personally identifying information provided through our Site (such as your name or email address) to any outside organization for use in its marketing or solicitations.
In addition, JTB World may also share aggregate information about its customers and its web site visitors to advertisers, business partners, and other third parties. For example, we might share that our users are x percent PCs users and y percent Macintosh users. None of this information, however, will contain personal, identifying information about our users.
Third Party Links
jtbworld.com does provide links to other sites. Other Internet sites and services have separate privacy and data collection practices. Once you leave jtbword.com, JTB World cannot control, and has no responsibility for, the privacy policies or data collection activities at another site.
Cookies
At times, we will use a feature on your web browser to send your computer a "cookie".
A cookie is a small text file that a website saves on your computer or mobile device when you visit the site. It enables the website to remember your actions and preferences (such as login, language, font size and other display preferences) over a period of time, so you don’t have to keep re-entering them whenever you come back to the site or browse from one page to another.
We do not use cookies to retrieve any personal information from your computer. We only use cookies to learn ways to enhance our Sites, and to give you better, more personalized service while in our web site.
You can control and/or delete cookies as you wish – for details, see aboutcookies.org. You can delete all cookies that are already on your computer and you can set most browsers to prevent them from being placed. If you do this, however, you may have to manually adjust some preferences every time you visit a site and some services and functionalities may not work.
Third parties may serve content and advertisements, collect information directly from visitors, and place or recognize cookies on visitors’ browsers.
Retention of Data
We will retain your Personal Data only for as long as is necessary. We will retain and use your Personal Data to the extent necessary to comply with our legal obligations (for example, if we are required to retain your data to comply with applicable laws), resolve disputes, and enforce our legal agreements and policies.
Children's Privacy Protection
JTB World is sensitive to the heightened need to protect the privacy of children under the age of 13. The vast majority of the material on our web site is not intended for children and is not targeted to children under the age of 13. We do not knowingly collect data from children and, if we learn that we have received personal data from a child, we will remove this information from our database.
GDPR (General Data Protection Regulation) Compliance
JTB World is GDPR compliant.
Transfer Of Data
Your information, including Personal Data, may be transferred to — and maintained on — computers located outside of your state, province, country or other governmental jurisdiction where the data protection laws may differ than those from your jurisdiction.
We will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this Privacy Policy and no transfer of your Personal Data will take place to an organization or a country unless there are adequate controls in place including the security of your data and other personal information.
Your consent to this Privacy Policy followed by your submission of such information represents your agreement to that transfer.
Disclosure Of Data
Business Transaction. If we are involved in a merger, acquisition or asset sale, your Personal Data may be transferred. We will provide notice before your Personal Data is transferred and becomes subject to a different Privacy Policy.
Disclosure for Law Enforcement. Under certain circumstances, we may be required to disclose your Personal Data if required to do so by law or in response to valid requests by public authorities (e.g. a court or a government agency).
Security Of Data
The security of your data is important to us, but remember that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Data, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.
Legal Basis for Processing Personal Data Under General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR)
If you are from the European Economic Area (EEA), JTB World's legal basis for collecting and using the personal information described in this Privacy Policy depends on the Personal Data we collect and the specific context in which we collect it.
JTB World may process your Personal Data because:
We need to perform a contract with you
You have given us permission to do so
The processing is in our legitimate interests and it's not overridden by your rights
For payment processing purposes
To comply with the law
Your Data Protection Rights Under General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR)
If you are a resident of the European Economic Area (EEA), you have certain data protection rights. JTB World aims to take reasonable steps to allow you to correct, amend, delete, or limit the use of your Personal Data.
If you wish to be informed what Personal Data we hold about you and if you want it to be removed from our systems, please contact us.
In certain circumstances, you have the following data protection rights:
The right to access, update or to delete the information we have on you.
The right of rectification. You have the right to have your information rectified if that information is inaccurate or incomplete.
The right to object. You have the right to object to our processing of your Personal Data.
The right of restriction. You have the right to request that we restrict the processing of your personal information.
The right to data portability. You have the right to be provided with a copy of your Personal Data in a structured, machine-readable and commonly used format.
The right to withdraw consent. You also have the right to withdraw your consent at any time where JTB World relied on your consent to process your personal information.
Please note that we may ask you to verify your identity before responding to such requests.
You have the right to complain to a Data Protection Authority about our collection and use of your Personal Data. For more information, please contact your local data protection authority in the European Economic Area (EEA).
Service Providers
We may employ third party companies and individuals to facilitate our Service ("Service Providers"), to provide the Service on our behalf, to perform Service-related services or to assist us in analyzing how our Service is used.
These third parties have access to your Personal Data only to perform these tasks on our behalf and are obligated not to disclose or use it for any other purpose.
Analytics
We may use third-party Service Providers to monitor and analyze the use of our Service.
Google Analytics
Google Analytics is a web analytics service offered by Google that tracks and reports website traffic. Google uses the data collected to track and monitor the use of our Service. This data is shared with other Google services. Google may use the collected data to contextualize and personalize the ads of its own advertising network.
You can opt-out of having made your activity on the Service available to Google Analytics by installing the Google Analytics opt-out browser add-on. The add-on prevents the Google Analytics JavaScript (ga.js, analytics.js, and dc.js) from sharing information with Google Analytics about visits activity.
For more information on the privacy practices of Google, please visit the Google Privacy & Terms web page: http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/
Payments
We may provide paid products and/or services within the Service. In that case, we use third-party services for payment processing (e.g. payment processors).
We will not store or collect your payment card details. That information is provided directly to our third-party payment processors whose use of your personal information is governed by their Privacy Policy. These payment processors adhere to the standards set by PCI-DSS as managed by the PCI Security Standards Council, which is a joint effort of brands like Visa, Mastercard, American Express and Discover. PCI-DSS requirements help ensure the secure handling of payment information.
The payment processors we work with are:
Bluesnap
PayPal
share-it
Changes to this Policy
JTB World may from time to time revise its privacy policy. You should therefore periodically visit this page, so you are aware of any such revisions. We will not, however, use your existing information in a manner not previously disclosed. You will be advised and have the opportunity to opt out of any new use of your information.
Contacting Us. If you have any questions about our privacy policy and/or the practices of our web site, you can contact us.
Apps
Avanti Start-App
JTB ACA_db
JTB ACAD_db
JTB ADTListDefinition
JTB Align Plus
JTB AutoReset
JTB Batch Change for AutoCAD
Useful Links
AutoCAD informationSheet Set ManagerRevit informationAutoLISP / Visual LISPFree VBA code snippets for AutoCADArticles by JTB WorldExample of work by JTB WorldAutodesk Network License ManagerFlexNet / FLEXlm feature codes for Autodesk applications and other applicationsAutodesk Product KeysBricsCAD informationJTB World Apps Licensing
Blog Headlines
Subscribe to the blog
Latest news
2020-12-07 JTB FlexReport 2020.12.0 released. Time to upgrade or request a free fully functional trial. Your network license assessment companion.
2020-11-28 JTB LayoutsToDwgs 2.0 released
2020-11-28 JTB Sheet Set Creator 2.7.2 released
2020-11-22 JTB SmartBatch 5.2.4 released. Script and batch processing for AutoCAD,  BricsCAD, ZWCAD and more.
2020-11-20 JTB DST Tool 2.0.0 released
2020-11-01 JTB License Manager 4.5.0 released
2020-11-01 JTB EduFinder 2.0.0 released
2020-10-23 JTB ACA_db 6.0.1 released
2020-10-05 JTB Batch Change for AutoCAD 2.2.1 released
2020-10-04 JTB OffsetlnXref 2.3.0 released. Better Offset for AutoCAD and BricsCAD.
2020-09-26 JTB SSMPropEditor 2020.9.0 released. Makes it easy to edit properties on multiple sheets in AutoCAD Sheet Set Manager.
2020-09-12 JTB FixRefs 2.0 released
2020-09-03 JTB Pline Closure Report 1.1.1 released
2020-08-31 JTB Tool Palettes 2.0.0 released
2020-08-30 JTB Page Setup Fix 1.4.1 released
2020-08-18 JTB Current Folder for AutoCAD 1.6.2 released
2020-08-16 JTB Sheet Set Publish 2.6.3 released
2020-08-16 JTB Sort Table 2.1.1 released
2020-08-16 JTB Spot Elevation for AutoCAD 1.3.1 released
2020-07-26 JTB Raster2OLE 1.3.1 released
2020-07-25 JTB CAD Automation Tools 5.7.1 released. Batch create and update text and attributes or insert blocks on hundreds of drawings automatically.
2020-07-25 JTB Steel 1.7.1 steel shape drafting app for AutoCAD released
2020-07-25 JTB Align Plus 4.3.1 released
2020-07-25 JTB Batch Plot for AutoCAD 2.3.1 released. Mass produce PDF and/or DWF.
2020-04-10 DimensionPatrol updated. Highlight edited dimensions for AutoCAD.
2020-04-10 Timber Tool updated
